opskins.com 2019-04-26

# OPSkins™ Privacy Policy

OPSkins™ ("we", "our", "us") takes your privacy seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to see how OPSkins™ will treat the personal information that you provide to us either when using this website (the "Site") or in other circumstances when we collect data from you (including via email). We will take reasonable care to keep your information secure and to prevent any unauthorised access or use of it. All U.S. credit card and ACH payments on OPSkins™ are serviced by Norris Services LLC, which acts in accordance with all applicable data privacy laws and guidelines pertaining to such payments.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and the change will take effect once the revised Privacy Policy is available on this Site. The “last revised” date is at the bottom of this Policy. Therefore, please refer to this Privacy Policy each time you submit your personal information.

## What Information Do We Ask You to Provide?

We may ask you to provide information to us or collect date from you on different occasions, including at a number of points on the Site, such as when you purchase our products or services, e-mail us about your interest, purchase or use of our products or services, or register to receive or download information, newsletters or other documentation.

The information that you are asked to provide will vary depending on the reason for the collection. In some instances, for example, if you purchase goods or services from us, the provision of certain information will be mandatory.

As we require individuals to be 18 years or older to buy or sell items on the Site, we do not seek to collect information from individuals younger than 18.

Please note that if you choose to participate in any discussion forum on the Site you may disclose personal information about yourself to other participants. If you do so this is at your own risk.

In addition, if you pay for items using Automated Clearing House (ACH), we will collect your full name, email address, and necessary bank account information to allow for such a payment transaction.

## How Do We Use Your Information?

We will use your personal information for our legitimate interests to respond to your enquiries, to send information to you, to fulfil any contractual obligation to you, for research purposes, to send marketing information to you regarding our goods, services and related opportunities, and other reasonable uses by virtue of your affirmative consent.

If you purchase goods or services from us we may send you further information that is related to your purchase, by post, e-mail or SMS and, if you pay for the purchase via ACH, we may use the information you provide in connection with that payment to process your payment.

We would like to send you marketing information, by post, e-mail, or SMS. In addition, our affiliated companies and selected third parties would like to send you marketing information, by post, e-mail, or SMS. We will only allow them to do this if you have you have affirmatively consented to receive such information. Advanced Options

If you do not wish to receive any of the above information or be contacted by us in accordance with the above, please update your preferences here, select the “Unsubscribe” button on our email, or write to the OPSkins™ at the address below. Please note that certain notices are operational in nature, and cannot be opted-out of.

If you submit your views to us via our contact form we may circulate them internally for training and management purposes.

We review the Personal Information we collect periodically to determine its accuracy and whether it can be deleted.

We may aggregate the information you send to us with other data (so that you cannot be identified from that data) and use that aggregated data for administrative purposes and/or share it with other people. 

## With Whom Do We Share Your Information?

We may share your Personal Information with third parties who may help us operate the Site, assist us in providing you with our services, processing your payment, or help us assess your interest or satisfaction with the Site or our services. Such third party service providers may only use the information in accordance with their own Privacy Policies.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy or to otherwise protect our business, clients or users.

We may release your Personal Information to others (including law enforcement) to comply with the law or legal process; enforce or apply the terms of applicable terms of use; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

We may sell, transfer and/or disclose your Personal Information as part of a business divestiture, sale, merger, or acquisition of all or a part of our business. 

We may also share your information with third parties for marketing purposes as described above if you have consented to receive such information. Some of these third parties may be located outside of the Isle of Man or United Kingdom, including in countries where data protection laws might not exist or be of a lower standard than the EU.

## How Do We Protect Your Information?

We are committed to protecting your privacy and we implement various security measures in relation to our processing and transfer of personal data. However, the nature of the Internet is such that the data may in some circumstances flow over networks without full security measures and could be accessible to unauthorized persons.

## How Do We Use Cookies and Similar Technologies?

When you visit the Site, we may collect, process and use informing about you which may not personally identify you but which may be helpful for improving the operation of the Site, such as “cookies.”

A cookie is a text file that stored on your computer. As text files, cookies cannot read information on your hard drive, run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies let our Site remember your preferences or recognize you when you return. You can delete cookies or configure your computer to reject them, although this may disable the Site’s ability to manage individual sessions.

As do many internet sites, we gather other information automatically, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

There are “do not track” or similar browser choices available to internet users with respect to online web activity, but given the present lack of consensus of what constitutes an informed election, appropriate trigger or breadth of scope of such choice, our Site will not operate any differently when a “do not track” signal is received.

## We Are Not Responsible for the Privacy Practices of Third Party Links

This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements applicable on those sites. This privacy policy does not apply to information collected on third parties’ sites.

## How Can You Access the Information We Collect?

You have the right to access the information that OPSkins™ holds about you. OPSkins™ may require you to provide verification of your identity. After the initial copy, you will be required to pay an administrative fee (currently £10) for any additional copies of the information. To make such a request, please send an email to info@opskins™.com, or write us at “Data Protection,” OPSkins™, St Mary's, The Parade, Castletown, Isle of Man, IM9 1LG.

If you are a US California resident, you may have the right to request and receive certain information about a company’s disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing use, and your choices with respect to such disclosures. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to info@opskins™.com, or write us at “Data Protection,” OPSkins™, St Mary's, The Parade, Castletown, Isle of Man, IM9 1LG.

Please note that in certain circumstances OPSkins™ may withhold access to your information where it has the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

## How Do You Update Your Information?

In the event that there is a change to your personal information for example your contact details, please let us know of this by updating your details online here or writing to the attention of “Data Protection,” at the address provided below, so that we can keep your information up to date and accurate.

## How Can You Contact Us?

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, wish to stop direct marketing by OPSkins™, its subsidiaries or third parties or you wish to access or update your information, email info@opskins™.com or write to the attention of “Data Protection,” OPSkins™, Floor 4, Willow House, Cricket Square, Grand Cayman KY1-9010, Cayman Islands

Last revised: April 24, 2019
